Prophet T.B Joshua Ministering Prophecy And Deliverance In Jesus' Name
I'm seeing a person inside you. You were attacked.
Yes man of God.
There is a man inside you.(Yes sir)
It's like, you can love men, sexually and you can love women sexually.
Yes man of God.
Your wife has been with you for sometime but she is disappointed now.
Yes, man of God!
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prophecy And Deliverance In Jesus' name.
STANDARD FOR LIFE
Emmanuel! (God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Patrick Busima. I am 45 years. I am from Uganda.
Before I confirm the prophecy ; what I am going to say today, I believe it's going to set many people free,
who are in the bondage of the confession I am about to make.
Last time during the service, Man of God prophet T.B.Joshua
The Spirit located me and he came to me
and he prophesied that I have an attack of a man inside me, that cause me to have
sexual affection for both man and woman.
And then he said my wife is very disappointed
I confirm the prophecy to be true and I thank God who located me that day.
And today this morning , I am here to make a confession that will help set many people
who are in bondage without knowing.
Well it started way back when I was at the age of seven years;
Sexually abused by my elder brother.
Since then I got a different spirit of getting to be attracted to both men and women.
I grew up struggling. Later in life I got a sign that will trigger to have these feelings.
I would have strong itching in my private parts.
When I itch, that sexual urge will come over.
Any man seated next to me; I will feel strongly attracted.
Nomatter whether he is handsome or ugly, as long as I have that itching ,
it will trigger the affection.
And just like the prophecy was; it is an attack that comes, once it comes;
these strong feelings are there.
I have struggled with them for the last 38 years.
Mr Patrick Prophecy Confirmation.
38 years living under this kind of bondage.
I have prayed. I have fasted to get rid of it because I had kept it to myself but not until
the spirit revealed it. I got my deliverance that day.
Ok sir, could you give us an example, perhaps you are in a public place
when suddenly there is itching on your parts
comes with a very strong sexual urge.
What would then happen at that moment?
It could be either in a public meeting or public transport, you begin itching, all the next
is you need to speak and have a conversation with the person next to you, with the man.
and see if he can really be your friend. And you keep talking into a love affair.
What you are trying to say sir is that at that moment you can not control yourself
the urge is so strong that you would approach any man be him ugly, handsome
just to satisfy that sexual urge.
Yah at that point of cause you are possessed like the urge is so strong,
that you run desperately to at least speak to a man you are seeing next.
And that is how it happens all these years.
Now, what were the various ways in which you found yourself getting entangled with
these men. Were also for example using the internet to go out and meet some of these men?
Just share with us some ways in which you encountered with them.
The major way was just the physical meeting.
Apart from the internet; not very much on facebook and probably if I met one
and would give another one my phone would kind of call say can I meet you,
because it seems you are in the same class of this affair.
So people of God I hope we understand what our brother is saying after he was sexually abused
at the tender age of seven, by his elder brother, that was how this strange spirits
of men entered him and he has been battling these sexual urges for his fellow men for 38 years.
And any time these urges would come, they would come in the form of strong itch
on his private parts which will be accompanied by that strong urge and in that minute he is in a public place
he would be ready to approach men at any given point to try and try to begin a relationship with them,
which would later blossom into a sexual relationship with them.
I what to say that this spirit has greatly affected my marital life just like it was with the prophecy.
That we have stayed together in marriage for 20 years but it has been a big disappointment
in a way that; once I begin itching myself, maybe at night I go to the bathroom
I can spend like 20 minutes but the first 10 minutes will be scratching myself heavily.
By the time I come to bed, I will not have any affection for my wife
I will lose out an erection that I will not stand to have sex with her.
Slightly I doze off, a man will come in a dream will be having sex with me
So for 20 years you had zero affection for your wife as a result of this.
Now how were you managing this double life of being married and the same time
going after men in your personal time?
I what to say it's quiet a challenging situation
because this is something that is within you.
You can not share it with another person.
I mean you live a life of torture, but this attack once it comes you were able to go out but
you are trying to conceal it yourself, it's just a life of torture.
My wife never knew about it, she got to know about it now one and half months ago
when she got to know about it.
How she got to know about it; she lost her phone
then I offered to give her my old phone to put her sim card, to use it.
Now when she activated whatsapp and she got to know
and to read a love message to one of the men I was communicating with.
She was mad and she is like no I can't continue to be together with a homosexual
and then that was like the man of God prophesied
that was the hardest time and the divorce was the next thing that was to come.
So once your wife discovered this, one month and half ago, since then both of you have separated
because she was so angry as a result of this hidden life that she never knew about.
Yes. When she discovered, we separated.
So once again people of God we hearing this confession from our brother
which we believe serves as a great lesson for our viewers all over the world
and those present here now.
Brother you said on your own you tried to stop.
Can you just give us an idea of the effort you made to try and get out of this
and how each time you found yourself returning back to the same problem.
I tried efforts. Sometimes I would go in prayer and fasting
and kind of delete any connection I would think with any other person who would have this affection
but all of a sudden when I get these attacks, I will go back to look at these contacts
to make sure we are communicating or we are talking.
Weeks before even my wife discovered, I tuned on Emmanuel TV.
While I was watching, I watched a testimony of one person who had been delivered
from that spirit. I got interested.
I even recorded it to really see that ok
I can get deliverance if I went to Synagogue.
That increased my faith.
Even when my wife discovered it, one thing I told her was, give me an opportunity
to go to SCOAN and then we shall discuss other things.
That was all I could say.
Ok so you told your wife that before going ahead with the final divorce;
you wanted to first come to the SCOAN
Yes, that's what I told her.
Ok sir. Tell us ever since the prophecy and deliverance
last week, Sunday what are the changes you have seen in your life?
I have seen a lot of changes. Of cause the attack of the itching, is no more.
I got delivered from the touch on Sunday. I have lived normally because what would
drive me to the affection of my fellow man was the itching.
I would even get a bathing sponge to make sure I am scrubbing heavily
before I will do anything. But since Sunday that is history, that is the past.
Mr Patrick Prophecy Confirmation
So the itching is gone, the affection, the attraction to your fellow males has gone.
And how have you been sleeping since the deliverance sir? You said before even in the dreams
these men would be abusing you sexually as well.
What has happened to you in that area since the deliverance?
I have slept comfortably. I have not have those strange dreams not even....
You know I would sleep and my hand is kept here, but I am sleeping comfortably not knowing what's happening.
Wow let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ.
Mr Patrick Prophecy Confirmation
We give all the Glory to our Lord Jesus Christ for what he has done for our brother.
And in the light of the experience that our brother shared after the word of prophecy
came forth last week; Prophet T.B. Joshua actually invited our brother's wife
to come here to the SCOAN all the way from Uganda.
By the Grace of God she is here in our midst.
We would like to invite her to come forward right now.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
So madam, you are very welcome in Jesus name.
We want to thank you for honouring the invitation of Prophet T.B.Joshua to be here this morning.
If you please introduce yourself to us and tell us what can you say concerning that prophecy
that your husband received last week.
Emmanuel! (God With Us - Matthew 1: 23)
Kevin Busima is my name is my name.
I want to confirm the prophecy, but before that I want to thank Prophet T.B. Joshua
For the invitation, for sponsoring me to be here.
Who am I to be sponsored in this whole world to be here today? I am so glad
Praise Jesus! I am very honoured that I was invited.
May God bless Prophet T. B. Joshua for inviting me here.
I can confirm the prophecy.
On... one month ago, I discovered something.
But I have lived with Mr Patrick for the last 20 years in this marriage.
But we didn't have affection.
When I married him in the beginning it was ok. But after two years there was something
which was very strange.
We didn't have affection for each other. We used to sleep in bed but each of us at the edge of the bed,
you know these big beds. So there was no affection completely.
But we have been praying and believing God that maybe one day something will happen.
Me, I thought that Patrick was impotent and that is all I knew.
And we have been believing God. I didn't know his other side of the story
until one month ago, like he said, I was in town, the thieves snatched my phone cracked it down
in Kampala.Then I didn't have another phone.
I had a phone but they were not giving out sim cards
so he gave me his phone. When I perused through whatsapp, I found that love message
with another man. Actually I ran mad, I was so angry.So what I did, I got a phone
I called him, "You have an attraction to men."
He said yes. Then I just switched off my phone.
After switching off my phone, he kept on calling me. I didn't answer again.
I was just annoyed. I told him that now you come I want us to separate.
Then when he was on the way coming, I told him, "I don't want you to come here , I don't want to see you."
Then later on , he came. I said," Now what we have to do is for us to separate or we divorce."
But he said ,"Give me an opportunity, I have watched something on Emmanuel TV.
Maybe I will be delivered, I will have total deliverance."
But even when he said like that, I said "Yes ok fine, I have forgive you because that is who you are.
But I want you to move from this bedroom, go to the guest bedroom."
That is what I did. So he has been living in the guest bedroom. Then I remained in the main bedroom.
And I have been so angered.
My life, my spirit has been grieved. I have had a lot of sorrow upon my heart.
Mrs Kevin & Husband Prophecy Confirmation
Holy Spirit help me.
So we can really understand the emotions our sister is explaining, for 20 years
of marriage to suddenly discover the secret hidden life of her husband and the two actually
at a point of separation.
So now last Sunday after the church service, I switched on Emmanuel TV.
While I was seated in the chair watching, I saw the prophecy at that time.
Prophet T.B. Joshua prophesying that - you have a spirit man that loves man and women.
But of cause I had seen a love message but until I got that prophecy now.
Then now I confirm that hooo it is now true.
This man has been doing these things.
Now after that prophecy, I kept quiet. I thanked God that thank you for revealing this.
And then of cause I kept quiet. Now on Monday night at 11pm when I was in bed
about to sleep, I received a call.
When I got a call it was a number which is new . I responded but I couldn't really understand
the person who was calling me.
I kept on saying who are you. He said I'm evangelist
So you mean to say that on the following day, you received that invitation from the SCOAN
and that's how you are here today, to honour the invitation of Prophet T.B. Joshua.
Yes that is how I'm here today, I received that invitation.
And I want to thank God that I am here and I believing to be delivered.
Because myself I am in state of confusion, I have forgiven him but
I want Prophet T.B. Joshua, Man of God to have an opinion about my state.
That I have been in this marriage for all this time.
Because right now I am here and I'm believing God for deliverance.
Ok, so we understand your position our sister has taken here; that she has forgiven her husband
and now she is here she wants to hear the opinion of God to know the next step to take
concerning the separation that she had already concluded on after this hidden life
in her husband was discovered.
So once again madam thank you very much for honouring the invitation of Jesus Christ
to be here today and we believe that Prophet T.B. Joshua will still come into this issue.
And reveal God's opinion for you to know how to move forward with your life and marriage in Jesus' name.
Amen.
At this point we just want to hear another word from our brother
So sir what is your word of advice concerning this?
Mr Patrick & Wife Prophecy Confirmation
Just like I said in the beginning that the confession I am making is to help many people
who are struggling in bondage. It's a two way;
There are those who are struggling with addictions and yet behind every addiction
there is that spirit that needs to be dealt with.
Then there are those who are living with these people who are in these spirits of addiction.
My word of advice to both parties, first to the people who are discovering people who have strange
behaviour or character; before we rush to pass judgement over them,
we need to recognize what could been the cause . What is behind this.
These people need a lot of love.
For example; Prophet T.B. Joshua since I came, he has shown me love
from the time of the prophecy. I extended my stay in this place. I have seen deliverance
because the spirit recognized the spirit in me and it was dealt with
so let's not rush into judging people who are struggling in all forms of addictions,
homosexuality, lesbianism, drug addict, there is something hidden that needs to be dealt with
and also you may be there but struggling in one or the other with something that you have hidden yourself.
Many of us we have hidden, for example I have stayed for 20 years with my wife
but she didn't know that I'm struggling with that spirit until
Prophet T.B. Joshua was able to prophecy on me and the spirit came out, I am now delivered.
Mr Patrick & Wife Prophecy Confirmation
And finally sir what is the last word you would like to say to your wife as you are here in the presence of God?
My last word, I want to say to my wife is this ;
First of all I ask you again to forgive me. This has been a struggling journey.
But today as we speak it's life in the past.
The day I stepped in the arena of liberty and the prophecy came upon my life,
It changed everything.
I am not the past but I am in the present.
Mr Patrick & Wife Prophecy Confirmation
One other thing is; it's not that I don't love my wife,
I really love my wife. That's one thing.
I want to confirm to you that days before I came to SCOAN when she had discovered
if you gave me a second chance to go to SCOAN, I know I will get deliverance
and we can have and we can rebuild our lives
so I am only appealing to her and to the spirit of God
because we have come to the arena of liberty, that whatever happened in the past
may not carry today's present life and lets move out as new people, new couple.
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ.
So once again we are going to rest this case right now to hear the opinion of God
from Prophet T.B. Joshua. We are very sure that both husband and wife will return
to share a wonderful testimony in Jesus' name.
And people of God we want the advice that our brother gave to serve as a lesson
to those present here and all around the world.
There are many people who are under the influence of such evil spirits and
it's easy for people to look at their actions on the outside and judge or condemn them
but at the end of the day if we judge them, how will they be saved and how will they be delivered?
So people of God let this serve as a lesson to us that we as Christians,
we should hate sin but love sinners.
And definitely through love, that's how we can bring about deliverance
for people who are under the torments of such spirits.
But if we judge them, treat them as outcasts, disassociate ourselves from them
How will they be helped and how will they be changed?
So once again let's let this serve as a lesson to our viewers all over the world.
As Prophet T.B Joshua says, if we fail to realise that there are spirits that cause us to be bound
down in bondage we will continue to fight the wrong battle. Fighting flesh and blood.
Fighting brother and sister, fighting neighbour, husband and wife but if we realize that
the spirit is the one behind it we will deal with it spiritually and get a lasting solution
And we pray that this couple will continue to maintain the deliverance and make the Word of God
the standard for their lives in Jesus' name.
Testimony Continues
My name is Patrick Busima. I come from Uganda
The woman next to me is my wife.
And I came here on the 20th of May, 2018.
And the problem that brought me here was seeking deliverance.
Because I had lived a frustrated life.
Life of rejection and I didn't know the cause.
But during the mass service, and the Prophet T.B. Joshua prophesied to me
that I have a spirit of man living within me that causes affection to both woman and man.
I confirm that it was true. And again also said that your wife you were living with for long time
is disappointed, which was true.
And in the very service, the same prophecy, he invited my wife to come.
And I am glad that my wife came and we just met prophet T.B. Joshua
We are happy that the past is gone. We have reconciled. My wife has forgiven me.
We are newly wedded couple and we are believing for the best.
And we promise we are coming back the same place with a bigger, bigger testimony to the glory of God.
Amen! So let's briefly hear from your wife.
Emmanuel people of God.
Kevin Busima. The man next to me is my husband Patrick Busima.
I came here on invitation of the Prophet.
And I want to thank God that God has used Prophet T.B. Joshua to bring deliverance to our family.
We have been married for 20 years but our marriage has been pambe (swahili word meaning to cheat)
But I want to thank God. I had a lot of bitterness
But when we met Prophet T.B. Joshua , he has counselled us, he reconciled us.
I want to thank God that he has intervened in our marriage. I'm now happy.
And I love my husband and I have forgiven him.
Mrs Kevin & Husband Prophecy Testimony
Thank you Jesus. We rejoice with both of you greatly and right now we want to
briefly hear a word of advice from our brother.
My word of advice is this;
Given my situation, it was not easy to explain to another person because it was quite embarrassing.
But sometimes when someone gets to know about somebody's situation
it turns out to be a gossiping situation.
All I want to say is; If you know a person who has such a bad experience, all you need to do is
stand with that person in prayer. Pray for that person that God's intervention at the right time
will happen and this person will get deliverance.
And once deliverance comes, this person will be a new person because what he is
is not by his own wishes but there is a force behind just like in my case.
I had a force behind that could drive me to be... just those who have watched my prophecy
that my testimony, you can really see the details on how the force was driving me
into doing what I was able to do.
And worse still I had kept it as a secret from my wife until the prophecy came.
So people listening and watching, love the people and pray for them.
Avoid passing judgement. It is very bad, once you judge, you are stepping and standing in the position of God.
Because God loves all. Let's hate sin but let's love sinners.
I think that's the message I can give to those who are watching and viewing now
Otherwise thank you so much. We pray that God bless this ministry
to continue really helping people who are travelling from afar seeking deliverance to this place.
I want to say thank you Jesus. Thank you for the deliverance. Thank you for the reconciliation.
To my marriage and thank you so much and we are new.
And we are coming back here to testify of God's goodness.
The advice I would like to give is that, whenever we are confronted with this situations,
we have to wait upon the Lord. We should not be quick to go for separation.
Because for us we were into the house of God to seek God's intervention for what
he was saying about our situation. And in deed when I was at the time of testimony,
that is what I requested - what is God saying about this relationship of ours.
And I am happy that God has been able to say something and he is still saying something for us.
And I would like to advice all couples out there that let us always listen to God before
we rush to make the decisions in our marriages because for us as Christians
our battle is not by flesh or blood but it is spiritual.
So we have to always pray and let God always be in the lead and give us direction always.
Thank you very much. We know with what you have said, it's a clear proof that
experience is the best teacher and having advice all our sundry, we believe couples out there have learnt
lot of lessons. As you go as a couple to make the Word of God the standard for your life.
We pray that this relationship has been reconciled back to say remain permanent in Jesus' name.
And at least always have it at the back of your mind that better is not good enough
the best is always yet to come in Jesus' name.
Thank you Jesus!
Mr Patrick & Wife Prophecy Testimony.
TT Monica Asefa 23/02/19